Christina Lu

UX Designer

www.christinalu.design luchristina7@gmail.com

Summary

I am a financial reporter turned UX designer with 1 year of UX design experience, 4 years of data analysis experience, and 5 years of self-taught HTML/CSS knowledge. I stay up-to-date on design news and utilize design feedback to create functional and engaging experiences.

Work Experience

Bloc

UX Designer Apprentice

August 2018 - June 2019

- Applied an end to end product design process to build desktop and mobile designs aimed to save shoppers time, keep users organized, and display information strategically
- Defined problems and needs for each project resulting in focused and strategic solutions
- Met with a senior level designer weekly to discuss design critiques and receive feedback necessary for future iterations.

Pioneer Square Advisors

Senior Financial Reporting Associate

Jan 2019 - Present

- Effectively communicates and collaborates with internal, external, and multidisciplinary teams to handle client obligations resulting in high-quality customer service and zero-errors
- Solves clients' problems by creating custom reports with data displayed strategically in a way that is easy for the client to understand
- Reviews each detail of expense reports before they are delivered to the client to ensure each deliverable is entirely accurate

Financial Reporting Associate

Oct 2016 - Dec 2018

- Updated various accounting systems, books, and reports simultaneously to complete projects and tasks by their respective deadlines through time-management and organization
- Handled transactions and sensitive data with care by documenting the complex workflow

Education

California State University, Sacramento

Aug 2010 - May 2015

B.S. Business Administration (Finance)

BlocUX Design Certificate

Aug 2018 - Jun 2019

Skills

UX design, visual design, user-flows, storyboards, wireframes, mockups, responsive design, usability testing, prototypes, iterative design, communication, web/desktop and mobile design

Tools

Sketch, Figma, Adobe XD, InVision, Abstract, Zeplin, Github, HTML, CSS, Maze, UsabilityHub